Patrick Drury

Professional Summary

Completed an intensive data analytics training poised to transition education and background experience in an entry data analytics position in the healthcare industry.

As lead staff member, served four years of patient-centered experience within VUMC, supported by strong customer service and communication skills from 10 years of retail experience. Leadership experience both within VUMC and Home Depot fostering team-based, collaborative environments.

Work History

Vanderbilt University Medical Center - Nashville, TN

Associate Program Manager, May 2020 – Present

- Provide day-to-day technical support for the creation, coordination, and execution of the decision support program.
- Utilize REDCap, Visio, and other programming tools to build, modify, and streamline decision support tools to facilitate patient scheduling
- Utilize Excel (tables, Pivot Tables) and other functionalities to create uniform worksheets and update forms for use across over 100 different clinic locations

Technical Support Specialist, January 2018 – May 2020

- Served as Senior Staff Member, File Room Lead for the Breast Center film management team and trained and coached new hires
- Ensured that all imaging systems are functioning as expected for both providers and radiology team.
- Coordinated system updates & troubleshooting with Informatics leadership.

Electronic Imaging Technician, March 2016 – January 2018

- Requested, processed and imported Films and CDs
- Managed workflow of the Breast Center File Room to help ensure smooth workflow for our team with both hospitals and patients
- Troubleshooted any technical issues that arose

Home Depot – Nashville, TN

Department Supervisor, September 2011 – March 2016

- Supervised team of 5-8 associates in a department that grossed \$6-7 million per year on average.
- Trained and coached associates to manage inventory and customer service
- Communicated and implemented corporate management directives to team

Head Cashier, October 2009 – September 2011

- Supervised team of 40+ cashiers
- Managed workflow and scheduling
- Handled customer inquiries and complaints

psdrury@gmail.com 201-320-1269 LinkedIn: Patrick Drury

Data Analytics Skills

- Python
- SQL
- PowerBi
- Tableau
- Advanced Excel

Professional Skills

- Customer Service
- Data Entry
- Electronic Medical Records Systems
- Leadership
- Patient-Care
- Staff Education and Training
- Supervision
- Troubleshooting

Education

Nashville Software School

Data Analytics Bootcamp January 2020 – June 2020

Lincoln Tech

HVAC Certification 2006 - 2007